(Leonard:)Okay, we're headed out--
See you later.
(Sheldon:)Before you leave,
(Sheldon:)could you test these
noise-cancelling headphones?
(Leonard:)Yeah, sure.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Go ahead.
(Leonard:)Hello, can you
hear me?
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I haven't changed
the filter
(Leonard:)in the water pitcher
in two years.
(Penny:)Uh, Bernadette's nickname for
you is the virgin piña colada.
(Leonard:)Your George Lucas autograph
is really a "me" autograph.
Yeah, well, once I was too lazy
to walk across the hall,
(Penny:)so I used your toothbrush.
(Leonard:)Ooh, and one time
when you were asleep,
(Leonard:)Amy totally
took off her...
(Leonard:)And that's why
you're the best roommate ever.
(Sheldon:)Aw...
(Sheldon:)Now I'm sad I didn't hear it.
(Penny:)So what do you need
the headphones for?
(Sheldon:)Well, I've been
struggling for months